Speaker 1: congressman rokhana is in the arena now for more so thank you so much for your time today in your view should the u.s give tomahawks to ukraine
i actually agree
Speaker 2: with president trump's caution that was also president biden's caution i have supported every weapons package to ukraine i will continue to support that but we need to really pause before giving weapons that could go deep into russian territory and risking
Speaker 3: escalation so
I
Speaker 3: am actually supportive, in this case, of the president's judicious approach. Putin
has
Speaker 4: ramped up attacks on Ukraine, as you know, since President Trump came
Speaker 5: back to office. Should Trump give Zelensky what he wants, though? I mean, how do you think that would change Putin's behavior? Because at this point, nothing's been
Speaker 6: changing. In fact, at the last meeting in Alaska, he only ramped up the attacks.
Well, I
Speaker 7: think we need a
Speaker 2: consistent message. We don't need Vice President Vance dressing down Zelensky in the Oval Office. I think if we have a consistent view that we're going to support Ukraine, we're going to provide them with the military assistance that we have been, and we're going to be working with Europeans to do that, that is what's going to bring success.
Speaker 2: Putin to the negotiating table. I don't think we have to risk an escalation into a war deep into Russian territory to do that. And by the way, these Tomahawk missiles cost $2.5 billion each. I certainly am not sure that the Europeans or the Americans are going to be able to subsidize them putting aside
Speaker 8: the risk.
Speaker 5: Yeah, and President Trump for his part did acknowledge that the U.S. also needs a stockpile of those weapons. So at the end of that bilateral, President Trump was asked about Venezuelan President Maduro offering natural resources in mediation. I want to play Trump's response to that and then
Speaker 9: get
your
Speaker 10: reaction. He has offered everything. He's offered everything. You're right. You know why? Because he doesn't want to fuck around with the United
States.
Some very
Speaker 11: strong language there from the president. What do you think? I'm
less concerned
Speaker 12: about his language and more concerned about his actions. I mean, why is he ordering covert action for
Speaker 2: regime change in Venezuela? We just had the American people vote against regime change, against the deep state. The American people do not want regime change wars. They want us focused on spending money here at home, on dealing with the rising prices
Speaker 2: groceries and here we have a president giving 20 billion dollars to argentina and now talking about getting us into a war in venezuela while we have record inflation and housing prices going up and
the white
Speaker 13: house has not been explicit that they're doing this for a regime change they say they're going after these drug cartels but do you view it as the u.s going to war with
venezuela
Speaker 14: Certainly that's what all
Speaker 2: the reporting looks like. I mean, they are engaged in covert actions by their own admission. It's not just strikes on these ships with potential drug cartels. I mean, they're talking about action within Venezuela. They're talking about strikes within Venezuela. When is this country going to learn after 20 years in Afghanistan, after Iraq, after Libya, after Yemen? The American people are tired of overseas wars. They're tired of our jobs going offshore. And where they want us
Speaker 2: to focus is to spend money here at home to bring down grocery prices, to bring down housing prices, to bring down child care costs, to create jobs in America. I want
to get
Speaker 4: your response to what the White House press secretary, Caroline Lovett, has said about the Democratic base, saying, quote, the Democrat Party's elected officials absolutely
Speaker 15: cater to pro-Hamas terrorists, illegal aliens, and violent criminals. As you know, all week, Republicans have been labeling tomorrow's plan A NATIONWIDE NO KINGS PROTEST AGAINST
THE TRUMP ADMINISTRATION
Speaker 15: as a "Hate
Speaker 16: America" rally. I want to play some of
what they said. -We
Speaker 17: call it the "Hate
Speaker 18: America" rally because you'll see the hate for America all over this thing when they show up. -It's all the pro-Hamas wing and the, you know, the Antifa
Speaker 19: people, they're all coming out.
Speaker 20: -There's considerable evidence that George Soros and his network is behind funding these rallies.
Speaker 21: -The farthest left, the hardest core, the most unhinged in the Democratic Party, which
Speaker 22: is, you know, a big title,
Speaker 22: And, you know, no kings equal no paychecks. And
we should
Speaker 23: note that there is no evidence that Antifa
Speaker 24: is actively involved or organizing these protests at this point. How should Democrats be pushing back against this rhetoric?
These are
Speaker 2: patriots who are coming out. They are standing up as citizens for our Constitution. They're standing up for the First Amendment and freedom of speech, saying you can't just make comedy illegal. They're standing up to say you can't have masked ICE agents ripping away kids from their families. But you know what is sad to me is I have never denigrated
Speaker 2: ordinary Americans who voted for Donald Trump. I've said that we need to treat our fellow citizens with respect. I've actually gone into communities that have overwhelmingly voted for Donald Trump and tried to engage in dialogue. I was just on with Benny Johnson, who's a prominent podcaster for Donald Trump. What we need is less insulting in this country. What we need is less denigration of people who may not vote for us. And we need to start dealing with some kind of respect and civility for our fellow Americans who are patriots. And that's what I think this country deeply wants. All
right,
Speaker 25: Congressman Ro Khanna, thank you so much.